youngerpornstars.com 2012-11-01

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

WE'RE SERIOUS ABOUT YOUR PRIVACY!

WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?  
We have created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our practices with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal and non-personal information provided by visitors to our Web site. By using this site, you signify your assent to these our privacy practices and the terms and conditions of our Web site. If you do not agree, please do not use this site.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?  
Personal Information  
We only collect personal information from visitors to our Web site when they voluntarily provide it to us by completing our registration form or electing to use one of our services In doing so, we may require visitors to provide us with information including, but not limited to, their name, physical address, email address, birth date, credit card number, credit card expiration date, username, password, unique identifier (such as their social security number), and demographic information (such as their income level).

Non-Personal Information  
When visitors access our Web site, certain non-personal information may be collected from them including, but not limited to, their browser type (e.g., Netscape or Internet Explorer), operating system (e.g., Windows or Macintosh), IP address, and the domain name from which they accessed the site (e.g., lycos.com) In addition, we may collect information about visitors' browsing behavior, such as the date and time they visit the Web site, the areas or pages of our Web site that they visit, the amount of time spent viewing the site, the number of times the visitor returns to the site, and click-stream data. We use transparent tracking pixels to determine the number of Web site visitors that have been sent to us through our affiliate network. We do not track any information about visitors once they leave our site. We may use cookies (small text files that are stored on visitors computers when they access our Web site) to collect this information. Information collected through cookies may be combined with visitors' personal information. We may also allow unaffiliated third parties, such as advertisers, to serve cookies to visitors of our Web site. Visitors are always free to decline cookies, but in doing so they may not be able to use certain features on our Web site. The "help" segment of the toolbar on most browsers explains how to configure a browser to not accept new cookies, how to have the browser inform a user when they receive a new cookie, and how to erase cookies from their hard drives.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
Our goal in collecting personal information is to provide visitors with the most personalized Web experience possible and our advertisers with an efficient means to reach the right audience. No personal information will be provided to any third parties without the customer's permission. By knowing a little about our visitors, we are able to deliver more relevant content and advertisements, and provide better services. We may use information collected from visitors to our Web site for any of the following purposes: (1) to send visitors information and promotional materials about our company, (2) to contact visitors to our Web site when necessary, (3) to help diagnose problems with our server, (4) to administer our Web site, (5) to conduct internal reviews of our site (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to the site), (6) to help us better understand visitors' use of our site, and (7) to protect the security or integrity of our site. Non-personal information will be used for purposes of conducting internal reviews of the site, monitoring the site, and providing a greater online experience for our visitors.

WHAT SECURITY MEASURES DO WE TAKE TO PROTECT YOUR DATA?  
To help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data integrity, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect from visitors to our Web site. We use Secure Socket Layer technology to protect any credit card information you provide us. We allow access to personal information only to persons and entities engaging in activities provided for by this Privacy Policy. Visitors should consider any communication that they transmit to us (such as data, questions or answers, comments, suggestions, or communications submitted to a chat room) to be non-confidential. We will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to a visitor is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.

CHILDREN'S PRIVACY  
Protecting the privacy of children is VERY important to us. For that reason we do not structure any part of our site to attract anyone under the age of 21 and we do not allow anyone under the age of 21 to register and become a member of our site.

UNFORESEEN CIRCUMSTANCES  
In the event of a merger, acquisition, asset or stock sale, bankruptcy, or other asset transfer (regardless of legal formality), any of our assets may be transferred to a third party, including personal information collected from visitors to our Web site.

ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY TERMS & CONDITIONS  
By visiting this Web site, you are agreeing to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. By visiting this site, you also accept, without limitation or qualification, all terms and conditions concerning the use of this site. We may at any time revise these terms and conditions. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore periodically visit this page to review the then-current terms and conditions to which you are bound. To the extent that any of the third-party sites accessible through our Web site (such as our advertisers) have different privacy practices from those stated in this Privacy Policy, those third-party privacy practices govern the collection and use of information you provide when visiting those sites. We are not responsible for the policies, content, and practices of other companies.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
There may be times when we need to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. To ensure that you are aware of our current privacy practices, please bookmark this page and check back often.

HOW CAN YOU ACCESS THE INFORMATION WE HAVE COLLECTED FROM YOU?  
Visitors who wish to access or change the information they provided to our Web site, should visit the Customer Service section of this site and contact us via Email.

HOW CAN YOU CONTACT THE WEB SITE OPERATOR?  
You may access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, updating, and in some instances deleting from our system any information deemed inaccurate. You may request to access your information by sending a request to:

Cider Communications  
12000 N Dale MABRY HWY, SUITE 110  
TAMPA, FL. US 33618   
or e-mail: support@cidercom.com  

If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact us at the above address.
